[
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of the United States?",
    "answers": ["Washington D.C.", "New York", "Los Angeles", "Chicago"],
    "correctAnswer": "Washington D.C.",
    "correctAnswerID": 0
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using commas correctly?",
    "answers": ["She likes, to eat mac 'n cheese.", "However, he did not watch the movie.", "'What, is your problem?' Steve Harvey asked.", "Please I beg you to stop!"],
    "correctAnswer": "However, he did not watch the movie.",
    "correctAnswerID": 1
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using commas correctly?",
    "answers": ["", "", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "correctAnswerID": 1
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using commas incorrectly?",
    "answers": ["", "You can use commas like this, or you can use them like that.", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "correctAnswerID": 0
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using commas incorrectly?",
    "answers": ["", "You can use commas like this, or you can use them like that.", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "correctAnswerID": 0
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence does not need its comma/s?",
    "answers": ["", "Bob, the guy down the hall, wants you to quiet down.", "He likes cats, and dogs.", "I like ice cream, and I love pizza."],
    "correctAnswer": "He likes cats, and dogs.",
    "correctAnswerID": 2
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence does not need its comma?",
    "answers": ["", "", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "correctAnswerID": 0
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence uses commas in a list or series?",
    "answers": ["I like cats, but I love dogs.", "'Farewell,' he said, 'may we meet again!'", "John's favorite activities are running, reading, and writing.", "Mr. Edwards, the college's statistics teacher, is a nice guy."],
    "correctAnswer": "John's favorite activities are running, reading and writing.",
    "correctAnswerID": 2
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence uses commas in a list or series?",
    "answers": ["", "", "", "On friday nights I like to sit, watch a movie, and eat popcorn."],
    "correctAnswer": "On friday nights I like to sit, watch a movie, and eat popcorn.",
    "correctAnswerID": 3
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using a comma when addressing someone?",
    "answers": ["What's going on, Gerald?", "", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "What's going on Gerald?",
    "correctAnswerID": 0
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using a comma when addressing someone?",
    "answers": ["", "", "Are you okay, Timothy?", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "Are you okay, Timothy?",
    "correctAnswerID": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What change should be made to the following sentence? 'I like eating homemade cookies.'", 
    "answers": ["I, like eating homemade cookies.", "I like eating, homemade cookies.", "I like eating homemade, cookies.", "No change."], 
    "correctAnswer": "No change.",
    "correctAnswerID":3
  },
  {
    "question": "What change should be made to the following sentence? 'He wanted to visit Paris Niagra Falls and Petra.'", 
    "answers": ["He wanted, to visit Paris, Niagra Falls and, Petra", "He wanted to visit Paris, Niagra Falls, and Petra.", "He wanted to visit Paris Niagra Falls, and Petra.", "No change."], 
    "correctAnswer": "He wanted to visit Paris, Niagra Falls, and Petra.",
    "correctAnswerID":1
  },
  {
    "question":"which date is formatted correctly?",
    "answers": ["April, 20, 2022", "July 8 2015", "November, 21 2011", "March 3, 2019"],
    "correctAnswer": "March 3, 2019",
    "correctAnswerID": 3
  },
  {
    "question":"Which address is formatted correctly?",
    "answers": ["", "", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "correctAnswerID": 0
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using commas around an appositive phrase?",
    "answers": ["Mr. Edwards, the college's statistics teacher, is a nice guy.", "", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "Mr. Edwards, the college's statistics teacher, is a nice guy",
    "correctAnswerID": 0
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using commas around an appositive phrase?",
    "answers": ["Our classmate Bill is often forgotten by his peers.", "", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "correctAnswerID": 1
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using commas around an appositive phrase?",
    "answers": ["", "", "Charlie, my pet ferret, greatly enjoys sleeping.", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "Charlie, my pet ferret, greatly enjoys sleeping.",
    "correctAnswerID": 2
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence uses a comma with a coordinating conjunction?",
    "answers": ["", "I think, therefore I am", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "I think, therefore I am",
    "correctAnswerID": 1
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence uses a comma with a coordinating conjunction?",
    "answers": ["", "", "", "You can use commas like this, or you can use them like that."],
    "correctAnswer": "You can use commas like this, or you can use them like that.",
    "correctAnswerID": 3
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using a different comma rule than the others?",
    "answers": ["", "", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "correctAnswerID": 0
  },
  {
    "question":"Which sentence is using a different comma rule than the others?",
    "answers": ["", "", "", ""],
    "correctAnswer": "",
    "correctAnswerID": 0
  }
]